You will believe.
DragonHeart is a fantasy, action, adventure film directed by Rob Cohen.
In an ancient time when majestic fire-breathers soared through the skies, a knight named Bowen
comes face to face and heart to heart with the last dragon on Earth, Draco.
Taking up arms to suppress a tyrant king, Bowen soon realizes his task will be
harder than he'd imagined: If he kills the king, Draco will die as well.
Bowen, played by Dennis Quaid.
Draco (voice), played by Sean Connery.
King Einon, played by David Thewlis.
Kara, played by Dina Meyer.
Gilbert, played by Pete Postlethwaite.
Lord Felton, played by Jason Isaacs.
Dragonheart (stylized as DragonHeart) is a 1996 fantasy adventure film directed by Rob Cohen and
written by Charles Edward Pogue, based on a story created by him and Patrick Read Johnson.
The film stars Dennis Quaid, David Thewlis, Pete Postlethwaite, Dina
Meyer, and Sean Connery as the voice of Draco the Dragon.
It was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Visual
Effects and various other awards in 1996 and 1997.
The film received mixed reviews, with critics praising the premise, visual effects, and
character development but panning the script as confusing and clichéd.
It was a box-office success, earning $115 million worldwide.
It was dedicated to the memory of Steve Price and Irwin Cohen.
The film explores themes of swordplay, magic, kingdom, immortality, prince.
The tone is emotional.